<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WebMon</string>
    <string name="company_info">WebMon Limited (formerly WebMon Technologies Limited) is an Indian Multinational Corporation that provides business consulting, information technology and outsourcing services. It has its headquarters in India, Australia, Canada, Nepal, USA, UK, Switzerland, Spain, Russia, Germany, Netherlands, Japan, Brazil and lot more. WebMon is the child company of RonLi Inc which is one of the most aspiring company in IT World. WebMon was founded by Rupesh Bhandari with the motive of easing the internet activity. Under the license of WebMon many software(s) are distributed in the world. The company\'s rapid growth since incorporation has triggered a chain of products, acquisitions, and partnerships beyond WebMon\'s core search engine (WebMon Search). It offers services designed for work and productivity (WebMon Docs, Sheets, and Slides), email (Gmail/Inbox), scheduling and time management (WebMon Calendar), cloud storage (WebMon Drive), social networking (WebMon+), instant messaging and video chat (WebMon Allo/Duo/Hangouts), language translation (WebMon Translate), mapping and turn-by-turn navigation (WebMon Maps/Waze/Earth/Street View), video sharing (YouTube), note-taking (WebMon Keep), and photo organizing and editing (WebMon Photos). The company leads the development of the Android mobile operating system, the WebMon Chrome web browser, and Chrome OS, a lightweight operating system based on the Chrome browser. WebMon has moved increasingly into hardware; from 2010 to 2015, it partnered with major electronics manufacturers in the production of its Nexus devices, and in October 2016, it released multiple hardware products (including the WebMon Pixel smartphone, Home smart speaker, Wifi mesh wireless router, and Daydream View virtual reality headset). The new hardware chief, Rick Osterloh, stated: "a lot of the innovation that we want to do now ends up requiring controlling the end-to-end user experience". WebMon has also experimented with becoming an Internet carrier. In February 2010, it announced WebMon Fiber, a fiber-optic infrastructure that was installed in Kansas City; in April 2015, it launched Project Fi in the United States, combining Wi-Fi and cellular networks from different providers; and in 2016, it announced the WebMon Station initiative to make public Wi-Fi available around the world, with initial deployment in India.[6]</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string-array name="emails">
        <item>"@gmail.com"</item>
        <item>"@outlook.com"</item>
        <item>"@icloud.com"</item>
        <item>"@hotmail.com"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
